Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Reborn from the Ashes]
[ولدت من الرماد]
[Episode 18]
[الحلقة 18]
You've committed a grave crime and still want to be released.
لقد ارتكبت جريمة خطيرة وما زلت تريد إطلاق سراحك.
I am your father.
انا والدك
Did you ever think I was your daughter when you poisoned me?
هل ظننت يوماً أنني ابنتك عندما سممتني؟
And besides,
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك،
Su Qingran is already dead.
سو تشينغران ميتة بالفعل.
Yet you still blame me.
ومع ذلك ما زلت تلومني.
Ten years ago, I sent you to the countryside.
قبل عشر سنوات، أرسلتك إلى الريف.
That was because your grandmother was muddle-headed.
ذلك لأن جدتك كانت مشوشة الذهن.
She didn't listen to your explanation.
لم تستمع إلى شرحك.
If back then
إذا كان ذلك في ذلك الوقت
you had just spoken to me honestly,
لقد تحدثت معي للتو بصدق،
how could I have not believed you?
كيف لم أصدقك؟
You still don't know
مازلت لا تعرف
where exactly you went wrong.
أين أخطأت بالضبط؟
You unfilial daughter,
يا ابنتي العقيمة
put the knife down at once.
ضع السكين فوراً.
Are you planning to kill your father?
هل تخطط لقتل والدك؟
Unfilial daughter?
ابنة عاقّة؟
You couldn't even recognize your own daughter.
لم تستطع حتى التعرف على ابنتك.
And you expect others to fulfill this filial duty?
وتتوقع من الآخرين أن يؤدوا هذا الواجب الأبوي؟
Su Guang,
سو قوانغ,
look closely.
انظر عن كثب.
Am I truly your daughter?
هل أنا ابنتك حقاً؟
You...
أنت...
You personally abandoned Su Qingran in the countryside.
لقد تخليت شخصياً عن سو تشينغران في الريف.
And your favored concubine, Gong Xi,
ومحظيتك المفضلة، غونغ شي،
colluded with your confidant Ye Changyuan,
تواطأت مع صديقك المقرب يي تشانغ يوان،
selling her off to Begonia House.
بيعها إلى دار بيجونيا.
She suffered for years and was cruelly mistreated until death.
لقد عانت لسنوات وتعرضت لسوء معاملة قاسية حتى وفاتها.
You are the one
أنت هو الشخص المناسب
who set all this in motion.
من الذي بدأ كل هذا؟
She has been waiting for you to bring her home.
لقد كانت تنتظر منك أن تعيدها إلى المنزل.
But she never came back before she died.
لكنها لم تعد أبداً قبل وفاتها.
She hated you.
كانت تكرهك.
She hated everyone in the Su Family.
كانت تكره جميع أفراد عائلة سو.
You don't deserve to be her father.
أنت لا تستحق أن تكون والدها.
I...
أنا...
I only wanted to discipline her.
كل ما أردته هو تأديبها.
I never meant for her to die.
لم أكن أنوي موتها أبداً.
Who... who are you?
من... من أنت؟
Me?
أنا؟
I am the daughter of Wen Muchen, former Governor of Yunzhou City,
أنا ابنة وين موتشن، الحاكم السابق لمدينة يونتشو،
Wen Yueqian.
ون يويه تشيان.
It was you and Wanyan Lie,
كنت أنت ووانيان لي،
who conspired to poison the Qilin Army
الذين تآمروا لتسميم جيش الكيلين
and framed my father.
ودبّروا مكيدة ضد والدي.
You caused my father's wrongful death.
لقد تسببت في وفاة والدي ظلماً.
If you hand over the account book with Wanyan Lie's crimes,
إذا سلمت دفتر الحسابات الذي يحتوي على جرائم وانيان لي،
I might spare your life today.
قد أعفو عن حياتك اليوم.
How do you know about the account book?
كيف عرفت عن دفتر الحسابات؟
Wanyan Jin told you?
قال لك وانيان جين؟
If you want to keep a secret,
إذا كنت ترغب في الاحتفاظ بسر،
you must not do the deed.
لا يجوز لك القيام بهذا الفعل.
Where is the book?
أين الكتاب؟
Do you think I'd hand over
هل تعتقد أنني سأسلم؟
what keeps me alive so easily?
ما الذي يبقيني على قيد الحياة بهذه السهولة؟
I will not tell you.
لن أخبرك.
Let's see how long you can keep it.
لنرى كم من الوقت يمكنك الاحتفاظ به.
Lord Bai Ling.
اللورد باي لينغ.
I'll give you one more night.
سأمنحك ليلة أخرى.
Your Highness, Su Guang committed suicide out of guilt.
صاحب السمو، انتحر سو غوانغ بدافع الشعور بالذنب.
Who came here?
من جاء هنا؟
The crown princess came.
حضرت ولية العهد.
She? Could it be her?
هي؟ هل يمكن أن تكون هي؟
Or was it someone else?
أم كان شخصاً آخر؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Has everything been dealt with?
هل تم التعامل مع كل شيء؟
Everything was handled as you ordered.
تم تنفيذ كل شيء كما طلبت.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
Speak your mind.
عبّر عن رأيك.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I beg you to save my life.
أرجوك أنقذ حياتي.
I did so many dirty deeds for you all these years.
لقد قمت بالعديد من الأعمال القذرة من أجلك طوال هذه السنوات.
My loyalty was absolute.
كان ولائي مطلقاً.
Even without merit, I deserve some credit.
حتى بدون استحقاق، أستحق بعض التقدير.
Hmph.
همم.
You still have the nerve to ask me?
هل ما زلت تملك الجرأة لتسألني؟
Su Guang,
سو قوانغ,
I really underestimated you.
لقد قللت من شأنك حقاً.
You're bold enough
أنت جريء بما فيه الكفاية
to smuggle black gunpowder.
لتهريب البارود الأسود.
You expect me to save you?
أتتوقع مني أن أنقذك؟
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفا.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
for you,
لك،
I poisoned the entire Qilin Army.
لقد سممت جيش الكيلين بأكمله.
Go fetch the wine quickly.
اذهب وأحضر النبيذ بسرعة.
Yes.
نعم.
Su Guang,
سو قوانغ,
you can be careless with your food,
يمكنك أن تكون مهملاً في تناول طعامك،
but not with your words.
لكن ليس بكلماتك.
What do I have to do with the Qilin Army
ما علاقتي بجيش الكيلين؟
and you?
وأنت؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
since you never did it,
بما أنك لم تفعل ذلك أبداً،
I suppose you didn't care
أظن أنك لم تكن تهتم
when Wen Muchen's account book
عندما كان دفتر حسابات وين موتشن
was placed before the Emperor.
وُضِعَ أمام الإمبراطور.
Didn't you already destroy the account book?
ألم تقم بالفعل بتدمير دفتر الحسابات؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
everyone fears death.
الجميع يخشى الموت.
If you save me,
إذا أنقذتني،
the account book will never be made public.
لن يتم نشر دفتر الحسابات للعامة أبداً .
Fine.
بخير.
I will save you.
سأنقذك.
Wanyan Lie,
كذبة وانيان,
the account book is still in my hands.
لا يزال دفتر الحسابات في يدي.
I can find it
أستطيع أن أجده
but I do not
ولكنني لا افعل
trust your tongue at all.
لا تثق بلسانك على الإطلاق.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Come with me to the Su Mansion.
تعال معي إلى قصر سو.
Yes.
نعم.
[Benefit the People]
[لصالح الشعب]
Conduct a thorough search of Su Mansion.
قم بإجراء تفتيش شامل لقصر سو.
Every corner
في كل زاوية
must be inspected carefully.
يجب فحصها بعناية.
If there is anything suspicious,
إذا كان هناك أي شيء مثير للريبة،
hand it over to me immediately.
سلمه لي فوراً.
Yes.
نعم.
[Suoqing Palace]
[قصر سوتشينغ]
Su Guang committed suicide.
انتحر سو غوانغ.
Wanyan Lie set fire to Su Mansion.
أشعلت وانيان لي النار في قصر سو.
He probably didn't find it.
ربما لم يعثر عليه.
Wanyan Jin has been interrogating Su Guang.
كان Wanyan Jin يستجوب Su Guang.
Could it be that he broke Su Guang's silence early
هل يُعقل أنه كسر صمت سو غوانغ مبكراً؟
and got the account book?
وهل حصلت على دفتر الحسابات؟
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
I heard
سمعت
Su Guang took his own life in prison.
انتحر سو غوانغ في السجن.
Since our cooperation went well,
بما أن تعاوننا سار على ما يرام،
how about we share a drink together?
ما رأيك أن نشرب مشروباً معاً؟
I fear your intention lies not in the wine.
أخشى أن نيتك لا تكمن في النبيذ.
Why wouldn't it be?
لماذا لا يكون كذلك؟
Today we speak only of romance, not of mundane affairs.
اليوم نتحدث فقط عن الرومانسية، وليس عن الأمور الدنيوية.
I salute you. Let's not leave until we're drunk.
أحييك. لن نغادر حتى نثمل.
Your tolerance is really low.
مستوى تحملك منخفض للغاية.
With one pot of wine, you're already drunk.
بمجرد شرب كأس واحد من النبيذ، ستكون ثملاً بالفعل.
She was looking for the account book. So the one who took it isn't her.
كانت تبحث عن دفتر الحسابات. لذا، من أخذه ليست هي.
But where exactly did Wanyan Jin hide the account book?
لكن أين أخفى وانيان جين دفتر الحسابات تحديداً؟
Why did I search the whole house but still couldn't find it?
لماذا بحثت في المنزل بأكمله ولم أجده؟
Could it be that he never took it?
هل من الممكن أنه لم يأخذها أبدًا؟
Could it be that Wanyan Lie really burn it in that fire?
هل يعقل أن يقوم وانيان لي بحرقها فعلاً في تلك النار؟
It's a futile effort.
إنه جهد عبثي.
After all that trouble, I still failed to find it.
بعد كل هذا العناء، ما زلتُ عاجزاً عن إيجاده.
Then just have a drink.
ثم تناول مشروبًا.
My head feels so dizzy.
أشعر بدوار شديد في رأسي.
Trying to steal a chicken but losing the rice.
محاولة سرقة دجاجة ولكن خسارة الأرز.
You wanted to get me drunk,
أردتَ أن تسكري،
but you got drunk in the end.
لكنك سكرت في النهاية.
I'm not drunk.
أنا لست في حالة سكر.
Could it be that when she's drunk, she answers questions in reverse?
هل من الممكن أنها عندما تكون ثملة، تجيب على الأسئلة بشكل معكوس؟
Am I your husband?
هل انا زوجك؟
No.
لا.
Are you
أنت
Wen Yueqian?
ون يويه تشيان؟
No.
لا.
Then you really are Wen Yueqian.
إذن أنت حقاً وين يويتشيان.
Do you
هل أنت
like me?
مثلي؟
No, I don't.
لا أنا لا.
You
أنت
like me?
مثلي؟
♪In this world, who exactly♪
???في هذا العالم من بالضبط؟؟؟
♪Pushed me into the abyss?♪
???دفعني إلى الهاوية ؟؟؟؟
♪The sky is silent, and the sea says nothing♪
السماء صامتة، والبحر لا ينطق بكلمة.
♪Who shows me mercy in this world?♪
???من يرحمني في الدنيا؟؟؟؟
♪Cold winds sweep across the wasteland♪
???رياح باردة تكتسح الأرض القاحلة؟؟؟
♪Mercilessly gifting me snow and frost♪
???يمنحني الثلج والصقيع بلا رحمة؟؟؟
♪In this fleeting life♪
في هذه الحياة الزائلة
♪No mercy, no answers♪
لا رحمة، لا إجابات.
♪Yet one lamp shines, unafraid to go out♪
ومع ذلك فإن مصباحًا واحدًا يضيء، ولا يخاف من الانطفاء؟؟؟
♪Time can twist, but people aren't perfect♪
???قد يتغير الزمن، لكن الناس ليسوا كاملين؟؟؟
♪Who decides who comes and who parts?♪
???من يقرر من يأتي ومن يفارق ؟؟؟؟
♪It all rests on a single hopeful thought♪
كل شيء يعتمد على فكرة واحدة تبعث على الأمل.
♪Why fear one last breath?♪
لماذا الخوف من النفس الأخير؟
♪Love is brief, full of regrets♪
???الحب قصير، مليء بالندم؟؟؟
♪I paint the sky as a fan♪
???أرسم السماء كمروحة؟؟؟
♪To blow away nightmares and scatter the dust♪
???لإزالة الكوابيس وتبديد الغبار؟؟؟
♪Can't resist the fate of being separated♪
???لا تستطيع مقاومة مصير الانفصال؟؟؟
♪By distance♪
عن طريق المسافة
[Exclusive content rights reserved]
[جميع الحقوق محفوظة]
[by Youku Information Technology (Beijing) Co., Ltd.]
[من قبل شركة يوكو لتكنولوجيا المعلومات (بكين) المحدودة]